Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
- This Week, 1962-1963 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.32 (1962: Oct. 11)
  - Item 33: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.33 (1962: Oct. 18)
  - Item 34: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.34 (1962: Oct. 26)
  - Item 35: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.35 (1962: Nov. 1)
  - Item 36: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.36 (1962: Nov. 8)
  - Item 37: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.37 (1962: Nov. 15)
  - Item 38: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.38 (1962: Nov. 22)
  - Item 39: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.39 (1962: Nov. 29)
  - Item 40: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.40 (1962: Dec. 6)
  - Item 41: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.41 (1962: Dec. 13)
  - Item 42: This Week, 1962; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.41 (1962: Dec. 20)
  - Item 43: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.42 (1963: Jan. 10)
- This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1963: Jan. 17)
  - Item 2: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1963: Jan. 31)
  - Item 3: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1963: Feb. 6)
  - Item 4: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1963: Feb. 14)
  - Item 5: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1963: Feb. 21)
  - Item 6: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (1963: Feb. 28)
  - Item 7: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (1963: Mar. 7)
  - Item 8: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1963: Mar. 14)
  - Item 9: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (1963: Mar. 21)
  - Item 10: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.10 (1963: Mar. 28)
  - Item 11: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1963: Apr. 4)
  - Item 12: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.12 (1963: Apr. 10)
  - Item 13: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.13 (1963: Apr. 25)
  - Item 14: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.14 (1963: May 2)
  - Item 15: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.15 (1963: May 9)
  - Item 16: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.16 (1963: May 16)
  - Item 17: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.17 (1963: May 23)
  - Item 18: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.18 (1963: May 30)
  - Item 19: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.19 (1963: June 20)
  - Item 20: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.20 (1963: June 27)
  - Item 21: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.21 (1963: July 4)
  - Item 22: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.22 (1963: July 11)
  - Item 23: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.23 (1963: July 18)
  - Item 24: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.24 (1963: July 25)
  - Item 25: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.25 (1963: Sept. 5)
  - Item 26: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.26 (1963: Sept. 12)
  - Item 27: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.27 (1963: Sept. 19)
  - Item 28: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.28 (1963: Sept. 26)
  - Item 29: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.29 (1963: Oct. 10)
  - Item 30: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.30 (1963: Oct. 17)
  - Item 31: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.31 (1963: Oct. 24)
  - Item 32: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.32 (1963: Oct. 31)
  - Item 33: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.33 (1963: Nov. 7)
  - Item 34: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.34 (1963: Nov. 14)
  - Item 35: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.35 (1963: Nov. 21)
  - Item 36: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.36 (1963: Nov. 28)
  - Item 37: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.37 (1963: Dec. 5)
  - Item 38: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.38 (1963: Dec. 12)
  - Item 39: This Week, 1963; Publication (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.39 (1963: Dec. 19)
- This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1964: Jan. 9)
  - Item 2: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1964: Jan. 16)
  - Item 3: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1964: Jan. 23)
  - Item 4: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1964: Jan. 30)
  - Item 5: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1964: Feb. 6)
  - Item 6: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1964: Feb. 13)
  - Item 7: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1964: Feb. 20)
  - Item 8: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1964: Feb. 27)
  - Item 9: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1964: Mar. 5)
  - Item 10: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1964: Mar. 12)
  - Item 11: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1964: Mar. 19)
  - Item 12: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1964: Apr. 9)
  - Item 13: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.13 (1964: Apr. 16)
  - Item 14: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.14 (1964: Apr. 23)
  - Item 15: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.15 (1964: Apr. 30)
  - Item 16: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.16 (1964: May 7)
  - Item 17: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.17 (1964: May 14)
  - Item 18: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.18 (1964: May 28)
  - Item 19: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.19 (1964: June 4)
  - Item 20: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.20 (1964: June 11)
  - Item 21: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.21 (1964: June 18)
  - Item 22: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.22 (1964: June 25)
  - Item 23: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.23 (1964: July 2)
  - Item 24: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.25 (1964: July 23)
  - Item 25: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.26 (1964: Aug. 13)
  - Item 26: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.27 (1964: Aug. 20)
  - Item 27: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.28 (1964: Aug. 27)
  - Item 28: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.29 (1964: Sept. 3)
  - Item 29: This Week, 1964; Publication (Box 131, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.30 (1964: Sept. 10)
- United Papermakers and Paperworkers Journal, 1957; Publication (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: United Papermakers and Paperworkers Journal, 1957; Publication (Box 131, Folder 4)
    Author: United Papermakers and Paperworkers
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1957: Autumn)
- Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1948: Jan. 3)
  - Item 2: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1948: Jan. 10)
  - Item 3: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1948: Jan. 17)
  - Item 4: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1948: Jan. 24)
  - Item 5: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1948: Jan. 31)
  - Item 6: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1948: Feb. 7)
  - Item 7: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.7 (1948: Feb. 14)
  - Item 8: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1948: Feb. 21)
  - Item 9: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1948: Feb. 28)
  - Item 10: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1948: Mar. 6)
  - Item 11: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.11 (1948: Mar. 13)
  - Item 12: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.12 (1948: Mar. 20)
  - Item 13: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.13 (1948: Mar. 27)
  - Item 14: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.14 (1948: Apr. 3)
  - Item 15: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.15 (1948: Apr. 10)
  - Item 16: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.16 (1948: Apr. 17)
  - Item 17: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.17 (1948: Apr. 24)
  - Item 18: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.18 (1948: May 1)
  - Item 19: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.19 (1948: May 8)
  - Item 20: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.20 (1948: May 15)
  - Item 21: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.21 (1948: May 22)
  - Item 22: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.22 (1948: May 29)
  - Item 23: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.23 (1948: June 5)
  - Item 24: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.24 (1948: June 12)
  - Item 25: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.25 (1948: June 19)
  - Item 26: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.26 (1948: June 26)
  - Item 27: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.27 (1948: July 3)
  - Item 28: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.28 (1948: July 10)
  - Item 29: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.29 (1948: July 17)
  - Item 30: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.30 (1948: July 24)
  - Item 31: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.31 (1948: July 31)
  - Item 32: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.32 (1948: Aug. 7)
  - Item 33: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.33 (1948: Aug. 14)
  - Item 34: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.34 (1948: Aug. 21)
  - Item 35: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.36 (1948: Sept. 4)
  - Item 36: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.37 (1948: Sept. 11)
  - Item 37: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.38 (1948: Sept. 18)
  - Item 38: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.39 (1948: Sept. 25)
  - Item 39: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.40 (1948: Oct. 2)
  - Item 40: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.41 (1948: Oct. 9)
  - Item 41: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.42 (1948: Oct. 16)
  - Item 42: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.44 (1948: Oct. 30)
  - Item 43: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.45 (1948: Nov. 6)
  - Item 44: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.46 (1948: Nov. 13)
  - Item 45: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.47 (1948: Nov. 20)
  - Item 46: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.48 (1948: Nov. 27)
  - Item 47: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.49 (1948: Dec. 4)
  - Item 48: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.50 (1948: Dec. 11)
  - Item 49: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.51 (1948: Dec. 18)
  - Item 50: Trainman News, 1948; Publication (Box 132, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.52 (1948: Dec. 25)
- Transport Bulletin, 1939-1941 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Transport Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Author: Transport Union of America
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1939: July)
  - Item 2: Transport Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1939: Aug.)
  - Item 3: Transport Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1939: Sept.)
  - Item 4: Transport Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1939: Oct.)
  - Item 5: Transport Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1939: Nov.)
  - Item 6: Transport Bulletin, 1939; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1939: Dec.)
  - Item 7: Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1940: Jan.)
  - Item 8: Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1940: Feb.)
  - Item 9: Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1940: Mar.)
  - Item 10: Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1940: Apr.)
  - Item 11: Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1940: May)
  - Item 12: Transport Bulletin, 1940; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1940: June)
  - Item 13: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1941: May)
  - Item 14: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1941: June)
- Transport Bulletin, 1941-1942 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1941: July)
  - Item 2: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1941: Aug.)
  - Item 3: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (1941: Sept.)
  - Item 4: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1941: Oct.)
  - Item 5: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1941: Nov.)
  - Item 6: Transport Bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1941: Dec.)
  - Item 7: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1942: Jan.)
  - Item 8: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1942: Feb.)
  - Item 9: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1942: Mar.)
  - Item 10: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1942: Apr.)
  - Item 11: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (1942: May)
  - Item 12: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (1942: June)
  - Item 13: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (1942: July)
  - Item 14: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (1942: Aug.)
  - Item 15: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.9 (1942: Sept.)
  - Item 16: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.10 (1942: Oct.)
  - Item 17: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.11 (1942: Nov.)
  - Item 18: Transport Bulletin, 1942; Publication (Box 132, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.12 (1942: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1949-1951 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1949; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Author: Transport Workers Union of America
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1949: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1949; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1949: Mar.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1949; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1949: Apr.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1949; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1949: June)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1951: Feb.)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1951: Apr.)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1951: May)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1951: June)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.8 (1951: Aug.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.9 (1951: Sept.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.10 (1951: Oct.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.11 (1951: Nov.)
  - Item 13: TWU Express, 1951; Publication (Box 132, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.12 (1951: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1952: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1952: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1952: Apr.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1952: May)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1952: June)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.7 (1952: Sept.)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.8 (1952: Oct.)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.9 (1952: Nov.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1952; Publication (Box 133, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1952: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1953: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1953: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1953: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1953: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1953: May )
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (1953: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (1953: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1953: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (1953: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.10 (1953: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1953: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1953; Publication (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.12 (1953: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1954: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1954: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1954: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1954: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1954: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1954: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1954: Sept.)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1954: Oct.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1954: Nov.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1954; Publication (Box 133, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1954: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1955: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1955: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1955: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1955: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1955: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1955: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1955: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1955: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (1955: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1955: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1955: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1955; Publication (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1955: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1956: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1956: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1956: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1956: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (1956: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (1956: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (1956: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (1956: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.9 (1956: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.10 (1956: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.11 (1956: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1956; Publication (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.12 (1956: Dec.)